[Music]
[音乐]
so welcome everyone
所以欢迎大家
to managing dependencies for spring
管理spring的依赖关系
projects with Gradle i'm jens straighter
Gradle的专案，我是Jens Straighter
or as you may know me on twitter the
或者您在Twitter上可能认识我
code generator I'm a developer advocate
代码生成器我是开发者拥护者
for Gradle I the company you may know
对于Gradle I，您可能知道的公司
from the Gradle build tool which we're
从我们的Gradle构建工具中
going to talk about today and Grail
今天要谈论和圣杯
Enterprise and today I have with me my
企业，今天我和我在一起
name's andy wilkinson I work for pivotal
我的名字叫安迪·威尔金森（Andy wilkinson）
where I primarily work on spring boots
我主要在春季靴子上工作
I'm also the lead of the spring rest
我也是春季休假的负责人
Doc's project and I wrote most of spring
Doc的项目，我写了大部分春季内容
boots Gradle plugin and the dependency
启动Gradle插件和依赖项
management plug-in that it uses that
它使用的管理插件
we're going to talk about today so the
今天我们要谈的是
way this is going to work is that Andy's
这将起作用的方式是Andy's
gonna do a little bit about the spring
会为春天做些事
dependency management plug-in I'm going
我要去的依赖管理插件
to talk about how the new features in
谈谈新功能如何
Gradle incorporate a lot of the work
Gradle整合了很多工作
that Andy's done and then we're going to
安迪完成了，然后我们要
talk about how you can migrate from the
谈论如何从
spring dependency management plug-in to
Spring依赖管理插件
some of the native Gradle stuff so just
一些本地Gradle的东西
to kind of see where we are who is using
看一下我们在哪里使用
the spring dependency management plug-in
spring依赖管理插件
now okay has anyone started using the
现在好了，有人开始使用
Gradle 5 native BOM support 1 okay so
Gradle 5本机BOM支持1
this is definitely the right talk for
这绝对是正确的演讲
for everybody in here so Andy get
对于这里的所有人，安迪得到
started all right Thank You Jenn um so
开始好了，谢谢詹恩，所以
perhaps a little bit bizarrely
也许有点奇怪
for a talk about Gradle this story only
谈论Gradle这个故事而已
all really begins with maven so spring
一切都从Maven开始，所以春天
boot is a project that is built with
boot是一个使用以下项目构建的项目
maven and it relies on some fairly major
Maven，它依赖于一些相当主要的
maven conventions and those are
Maven约定，这些是
conventions and functionality that we
我们的约定和功能
wanted to bring to Gradle users for
想带给Gradle用户
people who've made the decision to use
决定使用的人
Gradle rather than maven as they're
摇摇欲坠而不是行家
built all we wanted to be able to bring
建立了我们希望能够带来的一切
some of mavens advantages to the greater
一些行家的优势更大
world so as probably a lot of you know
世界，也许你们当中很多人都知道
if I should ask how many of you
我是否应该问你们几个
our spring boot users here pretty much
我们的春季靴子用户差不多
everybody and how many of you are
每个人，你们中有多少人
already using spring boot with Gradle
已经在Gradle中使用Spring Boot
okay good chunk of you okay so for those
好吧，你们好，好吧，对于那些
of you who are spring boot users it's
你们是春季靴子用户的
almost all of you you may well know that
你们几乎所有人都知道
there is a spring boot dependencies
有一个弹簧启动依赖
module within spring boot there is a
弹簧启动内的模块有一个
maven bill of materials now if you're
现在就可以使用Maven物料清单
using spring boot with maven you may be
与Maven一起使用Spring Boot，您可能会
more familiar with using spring boot
更熟悉使用弹簧靴
starter parent as your project parent
初学者父母作为您的项目父母
and it actually inherits from spring
它实际上是从春天继承的
boot dependencies so even if you're not
启动依赖项，即使您不是
using spring boot dependencies directly
直接使用Spring Boot依赖项
if you're using spring boot starter
如果您使用的是Spring Boot Starter
parent in a maven world as your project
在Maven世界中将父项作为您的项目
parent then you are in fact still using
父母，那么你实际上仍然在使用
the spring boot dependencies balm and
Spring Boot依赖润唇膏和
what a bill of materials does is it
物料清单是做什么的
manages dependency versions for you it
为您管理依赖版本
also manages maven plug-in versions but
还管理Maven插件版本，但
that's of no relevance if you're a
如果你是一个没有关系的人
Gradle user but that information is in
Gradle用户，但该信息已存在
there and does help you if you're using
在那里，如果您正在使用，确实会对您有所帮助
maven and the spring boot dependencies
Maven和Spring Boot依赖关系
balm manages both spring versions of
香脂同时管理两个春季版本
spring projects spring boot itself and
spring计划spring boot本身，
but also a large chunk of the rest of
但其余的大部分
the spring portfolio so this it manages
春季投资组合，因此可以管理
dependencies for spring data spring
弹簧数据弹簧的依赖性
security spring framework spring session
安全春季框架春季会议
etc etc and also we manage third-party
等等等，我们也管理第三方
dependencies so things like hibernate
依赖项，例如休眠
flyweight various JDBC drivers Cassandra
flyweight各种JDBC驱动程序Cassandra
etc etc they're all managed in there
等等等等，他们都在那里管理
which gives you a curated set of
这给您精选的
versions so that hopefully when you're
版本，希望当您
writing your app you don't need to worry
编写您的应用程序，您无需担心
about versions quite so much and in the
关于版本很多，在
balm we have over a hundred and fifty
香脂，我们有一百五十多个
properties so these are the things that
属性，所以这些是
you know there's a single property for
你知道有一个单一的财产
hibernates version and then those
休眠版本，然后
properties are used to control the
属性用于控制
version of 800 or so different
800左右的版本
dependencies and it looks a bit like
依赖关系，看起来有点像
this so this is a heavily reduced
所以这大大减少了
version but you can see up at the top an
版本，但您可以在顶部看到
example of couple of the version
几个版本的例子
properties so this I believe is a
属性，所以我认为这是一个
snippet from spring boot to 1/4 so you
从弹簧靴到1/4的摘要
can see that spring boot to four two one
可以看到那只春靴到四两一
four gives you Spring Framework five
四给你Spring Framework五
one six and also gives you time leaf
一六也给你时间
three oh ten and then you can see below
三哦十，然后你可以看到下面
an example of the dependency management
依赖管理的一个例子
so here we're managing a particular time
所以在这里我们要管理一个特定的时间
leaf dependency so this is the core time
叶依赖，所以这是核心时间
leaf module of the time leaf project and
时间叶项目的叶模块和
it's version is controlled by that
它的版本由
property so we're basically saying
财产，所以我们基本上是说
spring boots opinion is that if you're
如果你是
using the core module of time leaf the
使用时间叶的核心模块
version that you should use is three oh
您应该使用的版本是三个哦
ten and that's the one that spring boot
十，那是春天的靴子
this version of spring booth has been
这个版本的春季展台已经
built with and the version that we've
内建的版本
run all of our tests against as well so
还要针对我们进行所有测试
why is a bomb a good thing you know why
为什么炸弹是一件好事，你知道为什么
is this something that we thought you
这是我们以为你的东西吗
know that maven users could use why did
知道行家用户可以使用为什么
we want Gradle users to be able to use
我们希望Gradle用户能够使用
it as well what does it do for you as I
它对我有什么帮助
already mentioned it removes the need to
已经提到过，它消除了
think about versions when declaring
在声明时考虑版本
dependencies you can just say I want to
你可以说我想依赖
use spring boot two one for for example
例如使用弹簧靴两个
and you'll get a set of versions that we
您将获得一组版本的
have run all of our tests against and we
对我们进行了所有测试，我们
believe all work together it also means
相信所有人一起工作也意味着
that you get consistent versions across
您获得一致的版本
the libraries modules you'll sometimes
您有时会使用的库模块
see if you've got a bunch of different
看看你是否有很多不同
dependencies and they have transitive
依赖关系，它们具有传递性
dependencies on the same third-party
对同一第三方的依赖
project you might end up with you know
你可能最终会知道的项目
version one two three or is here you
版本一二三或在这里您
know version one two of a bit of it and
知道其中的一点一二
version one one of another bit of it
版本的另一点
sometimes you'll get away with that if
有时候，如果
they're two different maintenance
他们是两种不同的维护
versions you might just about get away
您可能即将离开的版本
with it if they're different minor
如果他们是不同的未成年人
versions or even worse different major
版本甚至更差的专业
versions you're very likely to run into
您很可能会遇到的版本
you know no such method errors abstract
你知道没有这样的方法错误摘要
method errors that kind of thing where
方法错误那种东西在哪里
there's an incompatibility and you've
存在不兼容性，您已经
got different mixed versions at runtime
在运行时得到了不同的混合版本
that we're never designed to work
我们从未被设计为可以工作
together using the bomb will mean that
一起使用炸弹将意味着
you know we provide an opinion about the
您知道我们提供有关
version of every single hibernate module
每个休眠模块的版本
every single time leaf module so if
每个单一的时间叶模块，如果
you're using the bomb either in maven or
您在maven或
in Gradle we'll make sure that all of
在Gradle中，我们将确保所有
hibernates modules are all at the same
休眠模块都在同一位置
version so it should eliminate these
版本，因此应该消除这些
kind of incompatibility problems from
某种不兼容问题
your build gives us detailed versions as
您的构建为我们提供了详细的版本
I've said that are tested and known to
我说过经过测试并知道
work together so these versions that you
一起工作，以便这些版本
get in the bomb other versions that
进入炸弹其他版本
spring boots unit integration tests have
弹簧靴单元集成测试有
all run against so we have a reasonable
所有人都在反对，所以我们有一个合理的
degree of confidence that they all work
他们都工作的信心度
together and which hopefully saves you a
在一起，希望可以节省您
bit of time and effort when you're
当你
integrating things but the other thing
整合事物，但另一件事
that's good about a bomb is it really is
炸弹很好，真的是
just an opinion and if you disagree then
只是一种意见，如果您不同意，
it's pretty straightforward for you to
这对您来说非常简单
override that opinion this could be
推翻那个意见，这可能是
because say for example there's a bug
因为例如说有一个错误
fix release of hibernate comes out and
修复了休眠的发布，并且
there hasn't been a bug fix release of a
尚未发布错误修复程序
spring boot to pick up that version of
春天的靴子拿起那个版本的
hibernate you can just say to spring
冬眠，你只能说春天
boots dependency management I want to
引导我想要的依赖管理
use hibernate 5 3 12 rather than the 5 3
使用休眠5 3 12而不是5 3
11 that you're giving me for example and
11你以我为例
using the properties and we'll take a
使用属性，我们将采取
look at this in a little bit more detail
仔细一点看
later using the properties declared in
稍后使用在中声明的属性
the bomb you can just provide a
炸弹，你可以提供一个
different version for that property and
该属性的不同版本，以及
then all of the modules will be that
那么所有的模块将是
version rather than the opinion from the
版本，而不是来自
bomb so this all began back in July of
炸弹，所以这一切都始于
2014 so almost 5 years ago now and when
2014年差不多5年前了
I was pulling this together for
我把这在一起
presentation I couldn't quite believe
我不敢相信的演讲
that this was 5 years ago and to begin
那是五年前开始的
with with the Gradle problem plug-in and
与Gradle问题插件配合使用
I can't remember why we did this and
我不记得为什么我们这样做了
when I think back it just feels
当我回想起来
completely daft and we use the
完全愚蠢，我们使用
properties file for managing all of the
属性文件，用于管理所有
versions with Gradle rather than reading
Gradle而不是阅读的版本
it from the bomb we like we took the
它来自炸弹，我们就像我们拿了
bomb from the source codes ran it
从源代码炸弹运行它
through some horrendous XLT
通过一些可怕的XLT
transformation turned it into a
转变成一个
properties file and then we wrote a
属性文件，然后我们写了一个
plug-in to read the properties file
插件读取属性文件
rather than just reading the bomb and I
而不是仅仅阅读炸弹，我
have no idea why we did that I can't
不知道为什么我们这样做，我不能
remember that was probably seemed like a
记住那可能看起来像一个
good idea at the time
当时好主意
so about five years ago we thought
所以大约五年前，我们认为
actually why don't we just use the bomb
实际上为什么我们不只是使用炸弹
file why don't we just use mavens well
文件为什么我们不很好地使用Maven
known well specified well-documented XML
已知的详细指定的有据可查的XML
format and see if we can complete
格式化，看看我们能否完成
consume that in a Gradle build so Phil
在Gradle版本中消耗掉它，所以Phil
logged this issue against the spring
针对春季记录了此问题
brute project and that gave rise to this
蛮横的项目，这引起了这个
separate Gradle plugin
单独的Gradle插件
we did it as a separate plugin because
我们将其作为单独的插件进行，因为
we thought that it might have benefit to
我们认为这可能对
the community beyond spring but-- and
春天以后的社区，但-
that has proven to be true we've had
事实证明，这是事实
people raising the issue of issues
人们提出问题
against the depends imagine plugin
针对Dependsimagine插件
who are building Android projects you
谁在构建Android项目
know something that's not even in the
知道甚至不存在的东西
spring community so while this is a
春天社区，所以虽然这是一个
spring Gradle plug-in if you have any
spring Gradle插件（如果有）
non spring projects being built with
正在建设的非春季项目
Gradle you can take advantage of the
您可以利用Gradle的优势
dependency management plug-in
依赖管理插件
functionality and it doesn't depend on
功能，它不依赖于
any of the rest of spring there's no
春天的其余时间没有
need to build a project that's kind of
需要建立一个类似的项目
tied to the spring ecosystem with it you
与春天的生态系统息息相关
can use it for whatever you like in a
可以将它用于您喜欢的任何内容
Gradle for project in a grade or five
一年级或五年级项目的摇篮
project hopefully you use the stuff that
希望您使用的项目
Jen's going to talk to you about instead
仁会跟你谈谈
so if you want to use the plug-in to
因此，如果您想使用该插件
import a bomb it's fairly standard kind
进口炸弹，这是相当标准的一种
of Gradle stuff to begin with you use
您开始使用Gradle之类的东西
the plugins block you specify the ID of
您指定的插件块的ID
the plug-in and the version that you
插件和您所使用的版本
want to use and then the plug-in
要使用然后再使用插件
provides a DSL to import maven bombs it
提供DSL来导入Maven炸弹
also provides a DSL that I won't go into
还提供了我不会涉及的DSL
details here but you can also declare
详细信息在这里，但您也可以声明
dependency management for individual
个人的依赖管理
dependency so if you don't have a bomb
依赖，所以如果你没有炸弹
that manages the dependencies but you
管理依赖性，但是你
say say you have some project that's
说说你有一些项目
internal within your enterprise but you
企业内部，但您
want to provide dependency management
想要提供依赖性管理
for it to make sure that you get this
确保它得到了
consistent set of versions that I talked
我说过的一致版本
about
关于
you can also declare individual
您也可以声明个人
dependencies manage individual
依赖管理个人
dependencies using the plugins DSL and
使用插件DSL和
here we're just saying we want to import
在这里，我们只是说我们要导入
a maven bomb and it's the old Spring
炸弹，这是旧的春天
Framework boots bring D dependencies so
框架启动带来了D依赖性
it's the exact same maven bomb version
这是完全相同的Maven炸弹版本
two one four and that will lead us leave
二一四，这将导致我们离开
us with a Gradle project with the
我们有一个Gradle项目，
dependency management that's been
依赖管理已经
imported from that from that bomb and
从那枚炸弹的进口中
the dependency management plugin
依赖管理插件
provides a new task for you similar to
为您提供类似于
how Gradle has its dependencies tasks
Gradle如何完成其​​依赖项任务
that you can run and it'll show you a
您可以运行，它将向您显示
list of all of the dependencies that
所有依赖项的列表
have been configured in your project the
已经在您的项目中配置了
dependency management plug-in also
依赖项管理插件
provides a dependency management task so
提供依赖项管理任务，因此
if you run that you will get output
如果运行，您将获得输出
showing the details of all of the
显示所有
dependencies that are currently being
当前正在依赖
managed these aren't necessarily
管理这些不一定
dependencies that your project is using
项目正在使用的依赖项
these are just ones that should you use
这些只是你应该使用的
a particular module that's managed then
然后管理的特定模块
the dependency manager
依赖管理器
plug-in will control the version of it
插件将控制它的版本
for you and you can see here a heavily
为你，你可以在这里看到一个沉重的
kind of reduced output there this is
那种减少的输出是
showing that we're managing some time
表明我们正在管理一些时间
leaf modules so we've got the time leave
叶模块，所以我们有时间离开
core time leaf module and the timely
核心时间叶模块和及时
spring 5 module both at version 3 or 11
版本5或11的spring 5模块
and then we've got some time leaf extras
然后我们还有一些额外的时间
which is managed as a separate project
作为单独的项目管理
has a separate release cycle so those
有一个单独的发布周期，所以那些
two have a separate version number as
两个有一个单独的版本号
those of you you may know your spring
你们这些人可能知道您的春天
boot users or maybe you didn't know
引导用户，或者您可能不知道
spring boot is already doing what I've
弹簧靴已经在做我所做的
just shown for you so if you're using
只是为您显示，所以如果您使用
spring boots Gradle plug-in so here
春季靴子Gradle插件在这里
using the plugins block ideal to bring
使用理想的插件块带来
from a boot with per tick tick to a
从每滴答滴答声的引导到
particular version if you apply the
特定版本（如果您应用
dependency management plug-in having
依赖管理插件
also configured your Gradle build to use
还配置了您的Gradle构建以使用
the spring boot plug-in it's kind of it
弹簧靴插件是一种
builds on spring boots kind of Auto
建立在汽车的弹簧靴上
configuration theme by applying the
通过应用配置主题
dependency management plug-in the spring
依赖管理插件春季
boot plug-in takes that as a signal you
启动插件会将其作为信号
want to use the dependency management
想使用依赖管理
plug-in to manage your project
插件来管理您的项目
dependencies so that applying of the
依赖关系，以便应用
dependency management plug-in the spring
依赖管理插件春季
boot plug-in kind of turns that into an
引导插件将其转变为
import of spring boots dependencies BOM
导入Spring Boot依赖项BOM
so it means that you can just specify a
因此，这意味着您只需指定一个
particular version of spring boots and
特定版本的春季靴子和
you'll automatically use that the
您将自动使用该
equivalent version so the same version
等效版本，所以相同的版本
of the spring boot dependencies BOM to
Spring Boot依赖项BOM到
manage your projects dependencies an
管理您的项目依赖性
important thing that I mentioned with
我提到过的重要的事情
the BOM support and one of the benefits
BOM支持和好处之一
of it is that the bomb is just an
炸弹只是一个
opinion and you can override it if
意见，如果您可以覆盖它
there's been you know if you need to
曾经有您知道是否需要
upgrade or downgrade for whatever reason
出于任何原因升级或降级
you can do that and the properties in
您可以做到这一点，并在其中的属性
the BOM strive to make that as easy as
BOM努力使之变得尽可能简单
possible and that's something that's
可能的，那是
supported in the Gradle world actually
实际上在Gradle世界中得到了支持
it's worth mentioning that AV in maven
值得一提的是，maven中的AV
the property override support only works
属性覆盖支持仅适用
when you're using a bomb as a parent or
当您使用炸弹作为父母或
as one of your ancestors be a parent or
作为您祖先之一的父母或
a grandparent or a great grandparent
祖父母或曾祖父母
if you import the bomb which is another
如果您导入炸弹，这是另一个
way that maven provides and if you're a
maven提供的方式，如果您是
so many of you here are spring cloud
你们这里有很多人是春云
users so you got a few spring cloud
用户，所以您有了一些春天的云
users here you've probably seen that you
用户在这里您可能已经看到您
in a maven project you imports but you
在Maven项目中，您导入但您
use typically you use spring boots
通常使用弹簧靴
starter parent as your parent and then
初学者父母作为您的父母，然后
you import spring clouds bomb and it
您导入弹簧云炸弹，它
kind of it brings all of the dependency
带来了所有的依赖
management together the spring boot bomb
一起管理弹簧靴炸弹
you can override properties because it's
您可以覆盖属性，因为它是
your parent but the spring cloud one you
你的父母，但春天的云你
can't because it's imported which is a
不能，因为它是进口的
shame it's a limitation of maven that I
真可惜我这是行家的局限
think there's an issue for it that they
认为他们有一个问题
may want to address but I the last time
可能想解决，但我最后一次
I spoke to someone in the Maidan
我在Maidan与某人交谈
community about it they said it required
他们说这是必需的社区
to change to the breaking change to the
改变到突破性的改变
maven model so it will require a maven
Maven模型，因此需要Maven
maybe Faldo
也许法尔多
perhaps you know a or maven five perhaps
也许你知道一个或行家五个
I don't know because they're not having
我不知道，因为他们没有
a four only so you can do this kind of
只有四个，所以你可以做这种
same override with the Gradle dependency
与Gradle依赖项相同的替代
management plug-in and you can use that
管理插件，您可以使用它
you can perform the override you know
您可以执行已知的覆盖
irrespective of how you use the bomb
不论您如何使用炸弹
there's no concept of a parent and
没有父母的概念
dependency management terms in Gradle so
Gradle中的依赖管理术语
when you use the dependency management
使用依赖项管理时
plug-in you can import and you import a
您可以导入插件，然后导入
bomb you can override a version and it
炸弹，您可以覆盖一个版本，它
looks a bit like this so here we have a
看起来有点像这样，所以在这里我们有一个
time leaf spring five dependency and I
时间板簧五依赖和我
haven't specified a version so this is
没有指定版本，所以这是
just kind of standard dependency
只是一种标准依赖
management by not specifying a version
通过不指定版本进行管理
you're saying let the dependency
你是说让依赖
management plug-in dictate the version
管理插件决定版本
so you can see here that the org the
所以你可以在这里看到组织
timely spring five module this little
及时春季五个模块这点
arrow indicates that we're going to use
箭头表示我们将要使用
three oh eleven release and that version
三哦十一发布和那个版本
has come from the dependency management
来自依赖管理
plugin you know can also see where it's
您知道的插件也可以看到它的位置
overridden some opinion so time leaf by
推翻了一些意见，所以时间流逝
default depends on slf for j1 7:25 the
默认值取决于j1 7:25的slf
dependency management plugin think she
依赖管理插件认为她
should be using one seven twenty six so
应该使用一七二十六
it's upgraded that dependency so there
它升级了依赖关系
you can see versions either side of the
您可以在
arrow so that's where the transitive
箭头，这就是传递的地方
dependency did have a version on it and
依赖确实有版本
the dependency management plug-in has
依赖项管理插件具有
said no I think you should be using this
说不，我想你应该用这个
new newer version because that's the one
较新的版本，因为那是一个
that's in the bomb so you can override a
在炸弹中，因此您可以覆盖
version and perhaps the most obvious way
版本，也许是最明显的方式
to
至
do that it's just to add the version to
这样做只是将版本添加到
the dependency so here I've said I'd
依赖性，所以我在这里说过
like to use timely spring 5 3 o 10 and
喜欢及时使用春季5 3 o 10和
if we look down the bottom we can see
如果我们向下看，我们可以看到
that I have indeed got timely spring 5 3
我确实有及时的 spring 5 3
o 10 but I've also got timely score
o 10但我也得到了及时的分数
module at 3 o 11 because the dependency
模块在3 o 11，因为依赖
management plugins opinion is that you
管理插件的意见是你
should be using 3 o 11
应该使用3 o 11
so you've expressed an opinion about the
所以您已经对
timely spring 5 module and the
及时的Spring 5模块和
dependency management plugin is
依赖管理插件是
respected that but you haven't said
尊重，但你没有说
anything about the core time leaf module
有关核心时间叶模块的任何信息
so the dependency management plug-in has
因此依赖管理插件
kind of clobbered that so you've now got
有点沉闷，所以您现在有了
a mix of 3 o 10 and 3 or 11 in your
在您的混合3 o 10和3或11
project you could add an explicit
项目，您可以添加一个明确的
dependency declaration on the time leaf
时间叶上的依赖项声明
module and express an opinion there but
模块并在那里发表意见，但
a better way to do it using the
一种更好的方法来使用
dependency management plug-in is to
依赖管理插件是为了
override the version instead so this is
改写版本，所以这是
the version that I showed you in the
我在其中显示的版本
original bomb so this is Gradle syntax
原始炸弹，所以这是Gradle语法
for set configuring an extra property so
用于设置配置额外的属性，以便
here we're setting the time leaf version
在这里我们设置时间叶版本
extra property to version 3 o 10 and you
版本3 o 10的额外属性，您
can see now that we have that's what
现在可以看到我们拥有的就是
we've got of both modules so the version
我们有两个模块，所以版本
less dependency declaration for timely
较少的依赖声明，及时发布
spring 5 has been upgraded or has been
春季5已升级或已升级
set at 3 o 10 and the time leaf module
设置在3 o 10和时间片模块
upon which it depends is also at 3 o 10
取决于它也是3 o 10
so you avoid this mismatch of versions
这样可以避免版本不匹配
by overriding the property rather than
通过覆盖属性而不是
by specifying the version on an
通过在
individual dependency declaration the
个人依赖声明
last thing that I want to talk about in
我想谈的最后一件事
setting the scenes of kind of where we
设定场景的类型
are today
今天
before Jen talks to you about the the
在Jen与您谈论有关
more interesting stuff that is new in
更有趣的新东西
Gradle 5 and stuff that's coming it's
Gradle 5和即将到来的东西
just a final feature that the dependency
只是依赖的最后一个特征
management plug-in has is that it brings
管理插件带来的是
maven style dependency exclusions to
Maven样式依赖项排除
Gradle and this is probably best
Gradle，这可能是最好的
illustrated with a hopefully fairly
有希望的公平地说明
simple example so here I have it's a
简单的例子，所以在这里我有一个
maven configuration so I have an
Maven的配置，所以我有一个
exclusions module and this example
排除模块和此示例
exclusions module has a couple of
排除模块有几个
dependence has a single dependency it
依赖有一个依赖
depends on spring core for 1:3 but
取决于弹簧芯的1：3但
excluding Commons locking because we
不包括Commons锁定，因为我们
want to use ASL foj
想要使用ASL foj
instead and slf O'Jays commons logging
相反，SLF O'Jays公共记录
SL f oj / j CL stuff instead of using
SL f oj / j CL内容，而不是使用
the commons locking api directly so if
公共锁定API直接，所以如果
we then depend on that project in maven
然后我们依靠Maven中的那个项目
and in Gradle and also pull in spring
在摇篮里，在春天也拉
beans so we're writing a spring app so
豆，所以我们要编写一个春季应用
our exclusions example module depended
我们的排除示例模块取决于
on spring core but in our app we also
在春季核心上，但在我们的应用中
need to use spring beans so we've got
需要使用四季豆，所以我们有
the maven configuration in the top left
左上方的Maven配置
and the equivalent Gradle configuration
和等效的Gradle配置
bottom right if using standard maven and
如果使用标准的Maven和
standard Gradle we look at those those
标准Gradle我们看那些
dependencies look at the dependency
依赖关系看依赖关系
graphs we end up with so at the top
我们最终得到的图在顶部
we've got the output of maven dependency
我们已经有了Maven依赖项的输出
tree and at the bottom we've got the
树，在底部，我们有
output of Gradle dependencies tasks
Gradle依赖项任务的输出
you'll see in the maven example we don't
您将在Maven示例中看到我们没有
have Commons logging but in the Gradle
有Commons日志，但是在Gradle中
example we do I think you could make an
例如，我们认为您可以
argument for either one of them being
论证其中之一是
right we don't really care what we
是的，我们真的不在乎我们
really cared about was that you got the
真正关心的是
same answer not which one you might
相同的答案不是您可能会选择的答案
consider to be right or wrong and Gradle
认为是对还是错和Gradle
is far more flexible than maven it was
比maven灵活得多
whilst not easy it was possible to
虽然不容易，但有可能
change Gradle exclusions behavior
更改Gradle排除行为
whereas I don't think it would have been
而我不认为会
possible to do the same for maven and we
可能对行家做同样的事情，我们
care in spring boots because we have as
照顾春季靴子，因为我们有
I'm sure almost all of you already know
我相信几乎所有人都已经知道
we have a bunch of starter modules and
我们有一堆入门模块，
in those starter modules we deployed
在我们部署的那些入门模块中
provide dependencies for you and in some
为您和某些人提供依赖
of those we have exclusions because we
其中有我们排除在外，因为我们
there are sometimes third-party projects
有时会有第三方项目
that have dependencies that are declared
具有已声明的依赖项
as mandatory when in fact they're not
实际上是强制性的
and in the way that we expect a stink
并以我们期望的方式发出臭味
typical spring boot user to use a
典型的Spring Boot用户使用
dependency that transitive dependency
依赖即传递依赖
isn't needed so we exclude it for you
不需要，因此我们为您排除了它
comments logging is the canonical
评论日志是规范的
example projects often pull in Commons
示例项目经常引入下议院
logging and then it gets in the way if
记录，然后它会妨碍
you're trying to root your Commons
您正在尝试扎根下议院
logging stuff into say slf a day and
每天将东西记录到slf中
then on into log back you need to keep
然后登录回去，您需要保持
Commons logging off your class path and
下议院注销你的课堂路径和
our starters really try to do that we
我们的初学者确实尝试这样做
have the maven enforce a plug-in
让Maven强制执行插件
configured to make sure that it
配置以确保它
doesn't sneak in so we're pretty
不偷偷摸摸，所以我们很漂亮
confident for maven users but you're not
对Maven用户充满信心，但您不是
going to end up with Commons logging on
最终以Commons登录
the classpath we wanted to be able to
我们希望能够的类路径
provide the same degree of confidence
提供相同程度的信心
for Gradle users which is why we added
对于Gradle用户，这就是为什么我们添加了
the exclusion support to the dependency
对依赖项的排除支持
management plugin to make things behave
管理插件，使事情变得正常
the same way a downside of that is the
同样的缺点是
variance it does slow your build down
变化确实会减慢您的构建速度
because there is more work to do it has
因为还有更多的工作要做
to go off and look at all the pom files
去看看所有的pom文件
to figure out what the exclusion should
找出应该排除的内容
be and then has to kind of mimic great
一定要模仿得很棒
mavens exclusion algorithm to figure out
Mavens排除算法来找出
what to keep and what to get rid of and
保留什么，摆脱什么，以及
then tell Gradle write these dependency
然后告诉Gradle写这些依赖
shouldn't actually be there it's been
实际上不应该在那里
optimized as much as we can but there's
尽我们所能优化，但是
only so much that can be done as a third
只能做三分之一
party plug-in rather than natively in
派对插件，而不是本地插件
Gradle itself so that really sets the
Gradle本身可以真正设定
scene I think with where we are today
我认为今天的情景
and why we got to where we are I'd now
以及为什么我们要到达现在的位置
like to hand you over to Jen to talk to
想把你交给简跟
you about the all the good stuff that's
你关于所有的好东西
in Gradle 5 and it's coming and that
在Gradle 5中，它即将到来
you'll hopefully look at and think and I
希望您会思考并思考，而我
say this as the author of the dependency
说这是依赖的作者
management plug-in so that you choose
管理插件，以便您选择
never to use it again I don't want to
永远不要再使用它，我不想
have to maintain that code so the more
必须维护该代码，因此更多
of you that use Gradle 5 dependency
你们中使用Gradle 5依赖关系的人
management stuff and give feedback to
管理资料并反馈给
the grail team about what's missing and
圣杯团队缺少什么
what you'd like to see the better and
您想看到的更好，
because something that's native to
因为某些东西
Gradle is used by all Gradle users
所有Gradle用户都使用Gradle
rather than just largely a spring boot
而不仅仅是弹簧靴
centric community I think is good for
我认为以社区为中心的社区
everybody
大家
so with that I'll hand you over to Jen
所以我会把你交给仁
to learn all about it thank you
了解所有相关信息，谢谢
so yeah the a lot of these features
是的，这些功能很多
ended up getting included in Gradle 5
最终被纳入Gradle 5
and even some of the more recent
甚至是一些较新的
versions and it's a it's a really great
版本，这是一个非常伟大的
story that we can tell here today
今天我们可以在这里讲的故事
because the spring dependency management
因为春天依赖管理
plug-in is actually one of the most
插件实际上是最多的插件之一
commonly used Gradle plugins like full
常用的Gradle插件，例如full
time and so those features are important
时间，所以这些功能很重要
to lots of people and as grayl has
对很多人来说，就像格雷
evolved we want to incorporate those
进化了我们想把那些
important features into the next and
重要功能进入下一个
upcoming versions and so we do that
即将推出的版本，所以我们做到了
through consuming bombs through some
通过一些消耗炸弹
better find great access
更好地找到便利
- or uh sorry fine-grained dependency
-或对不起细粒度的依赖
management as well as some improvements
管理以及一些改进
that have come to actually publishing
实际发布的
bombs and incorporating that back into
炸弹并将其合并回
other maven projects so the the
其他Maven项目，因此
long-term goal here is to be able to mix
长期的目标是能够混合
and match so you can have some projects
并匹配，以便您可以进行一些项目
using Gradle some projects using maven
使用Gradle使用Maven进行某些项目
and consumed for maven projects and then
并用于Maven项目，然后
publish back to them as well and so
也发回给他们等等
let's get started with kind of how
让我们从如何开始
native bomb support looks syntactically
本地炸弹支持在语法上看起来
it is a little bit different and since
这有点不同，因为
the long-term goal is to make this more
长期的目标是使这更多
compatible not only with maven but with
不仅与Maven兼容，而且与
other I what we're gonna call platforms
其他我要称为平台的东西
as well the syntax here isn't just to
以及这里的语法不仅仅是
like import a bomb it's to I to do a
就像进口炸弹，是我要做的
platform and so the platform includes
平台，因此该平台包括
maven bombs but also things like the new
Maven炸弹，但像新的东西
Gradle dependency management metadata
Gradle依赖管理元数据
format and in the future could apply to
格式，将来可能适用于
lots of other things as well and so the
还有很多其他的事情，所以
example that comes to mind for me is a
我想到的一个例子是
talk that I give about spring rest
我要讲的关于春天休息的话题
stocks and in that example demo project
股票，在该示例中为演示项目
I often override the version of groovy
我经常重写groovy的版本
and I today have it just as two five
我今天只有两个
seven it was just a point release that
七个只是一点点的发布
I'm trying to override but it actually
我正在尝试覆盖，但实际上
came to my attention a while back when
前阵子引起了我的注意
we switched from - groovy - 54 - - sorry
我们从-常规-54-抱歉
- 4 - 2 5 because the version of soccer
-4-2 5因为足球的版本
testing framework wasn't compatible so
测试框架不兼容，所以
we were getting these are I was getting
我们正在得到这些，我正在得到
these error messages about not being
这些关于不存在的错误消息
able to to compile and so what ends up
能够编译，所以最终
happening if I try to use this as an
如果我尝试将其用作
enforced platform it which is the most
强制平台这是最
similar behavior to the way that the
类似于
Pennsy management plugin works and that
Pennsy管理插件有效，并且
maven works in general is that I end up
Maven的作品总的来说是我结束了
even though I it specified that I want
即使我指定要
the two five seven version of groovy I
常规的二五七版本
end up getting this two five six version
最终得到这个二五六版本
because that is enforced and so who is
因为那是强制执行的，所以谁是
seen the Gradle build scan like this is
看到这样的Gradle构建扫描是
this new to everyone
每个人的新事物
a few people okay so this is a different
几个人好吧，这是不同的
dependency
依赖
than the than the one that Andy showed
比安迪展示的那个
and this is free if you do - - scan at
如果您这样做，这是免费的--扫描
the end of any Gradle build that's for
适用于任何Gradle构建的结尾
6r hire and I I would end up going
6r雇用和II最终会继续
through and trying to debug issues like
通过并尝试调试问题，例如
this by clicking any of those blue links
点击任何蓝色链接即可
and it'll pop out and say kind of where
它会弹出并说出类似的地方
that came from so you can see that some
来自，所以你可以看到一些
of these are coming from the spring boot
其中这些来自弹簧靴
dependencies or from other dependencies
依赖或来自其他依赖
that I had used in my project but the
我在项目中使用过的
very similar thing that happened here is
这里发生的非常相似的事情是
that I just just over the one particular
我只是在一个特定的
version what didn't happen is that I
版本没有发生的是我
didn't get any of the other versions -
没有任何其他版本-
so what you can do is you can try and
所以你可以做的就是尝试
force that one particular version of
强制使用一个特定版本的
groovy so you can do this by using force
时髦，所以你可以用力做到这一点
equals true which is a bit heavy-handed
等于true，有点用力
but you can also write a dependency
但是你也可以写一个依赖
management rule which I'll show a little
我将展示一些管理规则
bit later or a few different other
稍后或其他一些不同的地方
things to try and override that and so
尝试去克服它的东西等等
what happens now
现在发生了什么
actually let's try and guess so who
实际上，让我们尝试猜测
thinks that this is going to stay with
认为这将与
groovy - five six and who thinks it's
时髦-五个六，谁认为这是
going to do two five seven lots of
要去做二五七很多
people are not voting okay so it it does
人们不投票，可以
actually work in this case because we
在这种情况下实际工作，因为我们
are then forcing that version back to
然后强迫该版本返回
two five seven but you want to want to
二五七，但你想
be very careful in doing this because if
要非常小心，因为如果
you start forcing everything you're
你开始强迫自己
gonna end up with the same conflicts
最终会遇到同样的冲突
just at a different level and I so we
只是处于不同的水平，我所以我们
can we can start getting a little bit
我们可以开始一点点吗
more fine-grained here and even this
这里甚至更细粒度
particular version only does groovy okay
特定版本仅适用于常规
so all of the other dependencies that
所以所有其他依赖项
are related to groovy are not so it's
与groovy有关，所以
not doing everything in the group just
不做小组中的所有事情
the the group version which is what we
组版本，这就是我们
had talked about there so in order to do
曾经在那儿谈论过
that we have a couple other tactics as
我们还有其他一些策略
well the first one being that we can
第一个是，我们可以
delegate that to Gradle conflict
将其委托给Gradle冲突
resolution instead so by switching this
分辨率，因此通过切换此
from what I had before which is the
从我之前拥有的是
enforced platform so enforced platform
强制平台强制平台
means that I wanted to
就是说我想
all of those as requirements and by
所有这些都作为要求
removing that and going to platform we
删除并转到平台，我们
make those into recommendations which
提出建议
grade oils dependency management and it
等级石油依赖管理及其
can then decide which version to use so
然后可以决定使用哪个版本
if I do it this way it ends up with same
如果我这样做，它最终会以相同的方式结束
result but with fewer forces so it's it
结果，但是用更少的力量就可以了
is finding the two five seven version of
正在寻找的二五七版本
groovy we get the same issue where it's
groovy我们在哪里遇到了同样的问题
only that one library but it's using
只有一个图书馆，但它正在使用
Gradle instead so your you could end up
改为使用Gradle，这样您就可以结束
with fewer conflicts in the long run
从长远来看，冲突更少
okay so the next kind of progression
好吧，那么下一种进步
here is to actually override all of the
这实际上是覆盖所有
things in that group and so this is what
该组中的事情，所以这就是
I'm is a dependency management rule so
我是一个依赖管理规则
we we get a little bit more code here it
我们在这里得到更多代码
is not as easy anymore it's just doing a
不再那么容易了，它只是在做一个
little one line one line force but you
小一线一线力，但你
get a lot more control over exactly what
完全掌控什么
you want to do in this case we're going
您想在这种情况下要做的
to configure a resolution strategy for
为...配置解决方案策略
everything in the groovy group you can
您可以在groovy组中的所有内容
of course even make this even more
当然甚至可以使它更加
fine-grain and make pattern matching to
细化并进行图案匹配
do exactly which dependencies you'd like
确切地执行您想要的依赖项
here and get to this particular version
在这里并转到此特定版本
and then you can even add notes because
然后您甚至可以添加注释，因为
what inevitably happens with when you're
当你不可避免地会发生什么
trying to upgrade or even downgrade
试图升级甚至降级
versions is that you want to remember
版本是您要记住的
why maybe there's a particular issue
为什么也许有一个特定的问题
that happened in a later version so you
发生在更高版本中，所以您
want to lock at a lower version of a
想要锁定较低版本的
dependency and so we can both override
依赖关系，所以我们都可以覆盖
that version and annotate why we were
该版本并注释我们为什么
doing that and of course these are going
这样做，这些当然会
to expand out the more dependencies that
扩展更多的依赖
you're doing like this
你就是这样
so of course doing it this way will work
所以以这种方式当然可以工作
a little bit and yeah so that's that's
一点，是的，那就是
kind of a few different ways there are a
几种不同的方式
lot more in the documentation as well if
如果文档中还有更多内容，
you haven't had a chance to take a look
你没有机会看一看
at the new dependency management section
在新的依赖项管理部分
of the Gradle Docs you should there's a
在Gradle Docs中，您应该有一个
lot more included than than just a few
所包含的不仅仅是少数几个
simple examples here and even though the
这里的简单示例，即使
send
发送
taxes is not as easy to go through as
缴税不如缴税容易
Andy mentioned there is a big
安迪提到有一个很大的
performance difference here so for this
这里的性能差异
spring our stocks example that I've been
春天我去过的股票例子
using yeah this is what what came out of
是的，这就是结果
that dependency report and so you you
该依赖性报告，所以你
can't even read it but let's zoom in
甚至都看不到，但让我们放大
here so what happens is that there are
这里发生了什么事
90 different configurations that got
90种不同的配置
spun off here and this is a simple demo
在这里旋转出来，这是一个简单的演示
project but but like any much and this
项目，但非常喜欢这个
is not a this is the way that it had to
这不是它必须采取的方式
be done because in order to to analyze
之所以这样做是因为为了分析
the dependencies in the way that it was
依赖方式
happening like as a plugin author that
像插件作者一样发生
was the only way to do it but because we
是唯一的方法，但是因为我们
can now use some internal api's with
现在可以使用一些内部api
Gradle and just the way that the the
摇篮和的方式
team has constructed that we can get it
团队构建了我们可以得到的
much smaller in this case it all fits on
在这种情况下，体积要小得多
one page I don't need to zoom in anymore
一页，我不再需要放大
it's down to two twelve and I and even
下降到两个十二点，我甚至
within those you'll you'll notice a few
在那些你会发现一些
things here so I did include the links
事情在这里，所以我确实包括链接
to all of the build scans in here and
到这里的所有构建扫描
the slides will be published at the end
幻灯片将在最后发布
if you want to take a look you can click
如果您想看一下，可以单击
into those those are all public build
那些都是公共建筑
scans that you can take a look through
您可以浏览的扫描
and see the differences between those
并看到两者之间的差异
dependency resolutions but it's not just
依赖解决方案，但不仅仅是
about consuming maven bombs as well but
关于消耗炸弹，但
also about how we publish and interact
也关于我们如何发布和互动
back with with maven from from Gradle
来自Gradle的maven返回
projects and you may be wondering why to
项目，您可能想知道为什么
do this if you're of course on a library
如果您当然在图书馆，请执行此操作
author like someone on the spring team
像春天队里的人一样写
you publish things that way but it's
您以这种方式发布内容，但是
also useful for multi module systems if
如果多模块系统也有用
you're working with other teams and you
您正在与其他团队合作，而您
want to publish your your dependencies
想要发布您的依赖项
you can do that and so very similarly
你可以做到，所以非常相似
the maven published plugin has a which
Maven发布的插件有一个
the may be a public published plug-in
可能是公开发布的插件
itself is not new the thing that has
本身不是新事物
changed in Gradle version 5 too is that
在Gradle版本5中也进行了更改
you now have the option to use your
您现在可以选择使用
resolve dependencies versus declared
解决依赖与声明
dependencies what that means is that
依赖关系是什么意思
we've been talking about all of these
我们一直在谈论所有这些
Meyer not minor some in some cases the
迈耶在某些情况下并非不重要
differences between the dependency
依赖之间的差异
management
管理
for maven and Gradle so if you want to
对于Maven和Gradle，所以如果您想
make sure that the same dependencies
确保相同的依赖项
that were resolved not necessarily the
解决的不一定
ones that were declared because you've
那些因为你已经宣布的
got all of this version conflicts that
这个版本的所有冲突
you're having to to rectify you can use
您必须纠正才能使用
the this syntax to use what was actually
这种语法使用实际上是
resolved and make sure that you're using
解决并确保您正在使用
the same in both the Gradle projects and
在Gradle项目和
in maven projects and that then goes
在Maven项目中然后
even further into the this new plugin
甚至进入这个新插件
which is to publish java platforms right
这是发布Java平台的权利
now this is about publishing maven bombs
现在这是关于发布行尸炸弹
from Gradle itself and it might be a
来自Gradle本身，可能是
useful feature for some of you and yeah
对您和某些人有用的功能
so we've already seen what a maven bomb
所以我们已经看到了什么炸弹
looks like this is really just the the
看起来这真的只是
Gradle DSL syntax for for doing that and
为此的Gradle DSL语法和
so I it's not just maven bombs but
所以我不仅是行家炸弹，
eventually to get towards a new metadata
最终走向新的元数据
format that Gradle has defined and some
Gradle定义的格式和一些
kind of things that we notice as far as
到目前为止我们注意到的那种事情
limitations in maven and in and where
Maven以及在何处和何处的限制
we're heading with dependency management
我们要进行依赖管理
is to get into this new feature in 5:3
是要在5：3进入这个新功能
called feature variants and so feature
称为功能变体，所以功能
variants is again a very generic term to
变体再次是一个非常通用的术语
describe something that maven is doing
描述行家正在做的事情
but that all we also want to apply to
但我们也想将其应用于
other build system or yet build system
其他构建系统或尚未构建的系统
as well so if you're familiar with the
同样，如果您熟悉
concept of mavens optional dependencies
Maven可选依赖的概念
feature variants does that and more and
功能变体不仅可以做到这一点，而且
so the example that I want to use here
所以我想在这里使用的例子
is for databases when you have a library
有库时用于数据库
that you're publishing that supports
您正在发布的支持
multiple types of database connections
多种类型的数据库连接
like my sequel Postgres and Mongo for
就像我的续集Postgres和Mongo
example as a as a author when you're
作为作者时的示例
publishing those you want to be able to
发布那些您希望能够
to say that you can do either of those
说你可以做任何一个
but then you want to restrict or maybe
但是然后你想限制或者也许
not necessarily want to restrict but you
不一定要限制，但您
recognize that there are conflicts if
认识到如果存在冲突
you try to use more than one of those at
您尝试在其中使用多个
the same
相同
you can restrict that so if I is a
你可以限制它，如果我是一个
consumer and you were a library author
消费者，您是图书馆作者
that has published this and I try to
已经发布了这个，我尝试
import two different versions so in this
导入两个不同的版本，因此在此
case it's my sequel and Postgres then
如果是我的续集，然后是Postgres
it's going to give an error and so this
它会给出一个错误，所以这
is kind of an important part of Gradle
是Gradle的重要组成部分
strategy in general that we want to fail
我们想失败的总体策略
fast so rather than spending a lot of
快，而不是花费很多
time trying to debug this later down the
时间尝试稍后调试
line if we can know and recognize
行，如果我们可以知道和认识
earlier that you know there there are
早先你知道那里
two that are there are conflicts between
两者之间存在冲突
these two you can restrict that and
这两个你可以限制
prevent problems from happening to
防止问题发生
further down the line and so that
再往下走，这样
hopefully leads us into the Gradle
希望带领我们进入Gradle
module metadata format and so this is
模块元数据格式，所以这是
kind of an example it continues a lot
一个例子，它继续很多
further down that page obviously of how
在该页面的更下方显然是如何
we can take some of the things that
我们可以接受一些
we've learned from maven and some of the
我们从maven和一些
things that we've learned from Gradle in
我们从Gradle中学到的东西
the way that we define not only
我们不仅定义的方式
dependencies but other important
依赖但其他重要
metadata that are useful for publishing
对发布有用的元数据
and I kind of redefined that a little
我有点重新定义了
bit and so this is one of the important
一点，所以这是重要的之一
features that is coming in Gradle six
Gradle 6中即将推出的功能
and so this is why I named it five and
所以这就是为什么我给它起五个名字的原因
beyond so you can try it out right now
超越，所以您可以立即尝试
it's an optional feature that you need
这是您需要的可选功能
to enable in your Gradle build but you
在您的Gradle版本中启用，但是您
can publish to both formats and then
可以发布为两种格式，然后
starting in Gradle six this will be on
从Gradle 6开始，这将是
by default and so anytime you publish a
默认情况下，因此无论何时发布
anything in the maven format you'll also
任何Maven格式的内容
get a copy of this grid of my module
得到我的模块的这个网格的副本
metadata format a bit of a tongue
元数据格式有点麻烦
twister okay yeah so that is a little
绕线者好吧，是的，这有点
bit of kind of where Gradle is heading
Gradle前进的方向
and some of the things that you can do
以及您可以做的一些事情
to convert from dependency management
从依赖管理转换
plug-in to the the native support and
本机支持插件
there are of course lots of other things
当然还有很多其他的事情
that we mentioned in the documentation
我们在文档中提到的
can run some build scans to kind of see
可以运行一些构建扫描以查看
how that differs in your own and then
你自己有什么不同，然后
there are a few kind of gacho's perhaps
可能有几种凝乳
for migrating between these two and
在这两个之间迁移
maybe some things that we still have on
也许我们还有一些事情
the roadmap to to fix and so the the
要修复的路线图，因此
first one is exclusions and so
第一个是排除，所以
exclusions are still much harder to
排除仍然很难
define in Gradle and so this is one of
在Gradle中定义，所以这是其中之一
the the things that's on the road map
路线图上的东西
for the dependency management team to
供依赖性管理团队使用
try and make make a little bit easier it
尝试使它变得容易一些
is possible to define exclusions but it
可以定义排除，但它可以
ends up being a bit a bit harder in the
最终变得有点困难
end another kind of little one is that
结束另一种小家伙是
you'll need to remember to add a
您需要记住添加一个
different scope so in particular even
不同的范围，尤其是甚至
projects as big as micronaut for example
像微型鱼一样大的项目
didn't work getting the right
取得正确的结果没有用
dependencies included so you need to
包括依赖项，因此您需要
remember that the annotation processor
记住注释处理器
needs to be separated so this is
需要分开，所以这是
something that the that the plug-in does
插件执行的操作
I but that that Gradle doesn't do for
我，但那Gradle不能做到
various reasons so it's actually an
各种原因，所以实际上
intentional thing that we want you to
我们想要您做的有意的事情
think about which dependencies you
考虑一下你的依赖
actually want to use in each each scope
实际想在每个范围内使用
okay and because some of this is new so
好的，因为其中有些是新的，所以
Gradle 5 came out in November of last
Gradle 5于去年11月问世
year so it's not entirely new yet but
一年，所以还不是全新的
some of these concepts aren't aren't
其中一些概念不是
very simple we've been talking about
很简单，我们一直在谈论
just like one small portion of how
就像一小部分
Gradle works in general and even ideas
摇篮作品一般甚至想法
like like IntelliJ haven't entirely
像IntelliJ一样
caught up with some of these features I
赶上了我的一些功能
usually run things on the command line
通常在命令行上运行
but if you are using the Gradle support
但是如果您使用Gradle支持
that's kind of embedded in IntelliJ as
在IntelliJ中被嵌入为
well as even even the Eclipse versions I
甚至我的Eclipse版本
you may not see see the same dependency
您可能看不到相同的依赖项
reports
报告
this is something that we're working on
这是我们正在努力的事情
the issues have been filed we've reached
我们已经解决了问题
out to all of the IDE vendors to try and
向所有IDE供应商尝试
get this up to date thank you
得到这个最新的谢谢
and so the the last one that's probably
所以最后一个可能是
the the one that hasn't completely been
那个还没有完全被
been fixed yet that we still need to
已经修复，我们仍然需要
work on even a bit more is more about
更多的工作更多关于
overriding these version properties so
覆盖这些版本属性，因此
the light like Andy had mentioned the
像安迪提到的光
the way that that plugin works is very
该插件的工作方式非常
special it goes above beyond both what
特别是它超越了两者
Gradle and in maven we're doing and for
在Gradle和Maven中，我们正在为
upgrading versions I showed you a few
升级版本，我向您展示了一些
different ways that that can happen
可能发生的不同方式
but there are still some problems if you
但是如果你仍然有一些问题
want to downgrade your version and
想要降级您的版本，并
particularly because Gradle will by
特别是因为Gradle将
default wants to try and resolve this by
默认情况下想尝试解决此问题
going up
往上走
you have to kind of override force and
你必须要有一种超越力
these are actually listed in order of
这些实际上是按以下顺序列出的
what you should try to do so you should
你应该怎么做，所以你应该
try to write a rule first before you try
尝试之前先尝试编写规则
to to kind of have it heavy handedly
有点沉重地
force everything and then if you
强迫一切，然后如果你
absolutely need to exclude it and add a
绝对需要排除它并添加一个
different dependency but we are
不同的依赖关系，但我们是
hopefully trying to fix a lot of these
希望尝试修复很多这些问题
different issues and I think you know a
不同的问题，我想你知道
bit more about what the version version
关于版本版本的更多信息
properties are missing yeah I think it
属性丢失是的，我认为
is mostly the overwrite stuff but as Jen
主要是覆盖的东西，但作为仁
said the Gradle team have been really
说Gradle团队真的
receptive to feedback the dependency
接受反馈的依赖
management team cdric primarily who
管理团队塞德里克主要是谁
I've spoken with has been very receptive
我与之交谈过的很容易接受
to feedback but doing things in the
进行反馈，但在
Gradle way so they don't want to
摇篮方式，所以他们不想
replicate maven for good reasons you
复制Maven是有充分理由的
know if you like Gradle turning it back
知道你是否喜欢Gradle把它转回去
into maven it's not going to be a good
进入行家，这将不是一个好习惯
solution for you so if you have any
解决方案，如果您有的话
feedback of your own based on trying out
尝试后自己反馈
the stuff then in my experience it's
那么根据我的经验，
well worth
很值得
chatting with the gradle team
与gradle团队聊天
particularly the the the folks on the
特别是那些
Gradle team who work in the dependency
在依赖中工作的Gradle团队
management piece
管理片
I said yeah they're really receptive for
我说是的，他们真的很接受
feedback so if you try out any of the
反馈，因此，如果您尝试任何
stuff that Jen's talked about then you
仁讲过的东西然后你
know please do get in touch with them
知道请与他们取得联系
and again equally if there's anything
同样，如果有的话
that you think the dependency management
您认为依赖管理
plugin could do differently then you
插件的功能可能与您不同
know please let me know as well for
知道请也让我知道
those of you who are need to stay on
你们中那些需要留下来的人
Gradle 4 for whatever reason or can't
无论出于何种原因或无法做到，Gradle 4
use the native stuff in Gradle 5 for
使用Gradle 5中的本地内容
whatever reason but hopefully
出于什么原因，但希望
longer-term the dependency management
长期依赖管理
plugin can just kind of wither away and
插件可以消亡，
the native stuff will take over yeah so
本地的东西将接管所以
that's a really great point the best way
这是最好的方法，真的很重要
to provide feedback is actually to go to
提供反馈实际上是去
our forums so disgusting org and kind of
我们的论坛是如此令人作呕的组织和
ask any questions that you have the
问任何您有的问题
dependency management team is happy to
依赖管理团队很高兴
help we also have a dependency
帮助我们也有依赖性
management series which goes into a lot
大量的管理系列
more detail on a lot of the other
其他更多细节
concepts particularly things that are
概念，尤其是
kind of unique to Gradle itself and they
对于Gradle本身来说是独一无二的，他们
just published the first one on the
刚刚在
Gradle blog and we'll have at least I
Gradle博客，我们至少会有我
think we're looking at at least two more
认为我们至少还要看两个
to go into even some more of this new
进一步研究这个新事物
metadata format information in
中的元数据格式信息
particular and how that differentiates
特别以及如何区别
from maven bombs so right as the
来自Maven炸弹
conclusion here we hope that everyone
结论在这里，我们希望大家
can switch and if you can you should
可以切换，如果可以的话
because you'll get a lot of the benefits
因为你会得到很多好处
not only of performance but also being
不仅表现，而且
able to more tightly control what
能够更严格地控​​制什么
happens and yeah I think that is most of
发生，是的，我认为这是大多数
what I had and yeah so the the links to
我拥有的是的，所以链接到
the the Gradle org Doc's as well there's
Gradle org Doc以及
a really nice section on dependency
关于依赖的一个非常好的部分
management particularly on managing
管理，尤其是管理
transitive dependencies which I've
我的传递依赖
linked on most of those slides as well
以及大多数幻灯片上的链接
the slides will go out via my Twitter
幻灯片将通过我的Twitter发出
account so if you check there on code
帐户，所以如果您在代码上检查
generator it'll go out in a couple
发电机，它会在几个时间里熄灭
minutes once we've finished the slide or
分钟，我们完成幻灯片或
finish the presentation is I know this
完成演示文稿是我知道的吗
is a lot
很多
this is a really tough topic in in
这是一个非常艰难的话题
building building software in general
一般建筑软件
all right thank you everybody
好的，谢谢大家
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]